One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Pearl
بيرل-سان
They wanna fight, too!
!يبتغون القتال أيضًا
I'm getting fired up!
!بدأتُ أتحمّس
Boss Man! It's a deal, right?
يا عم، أستفي بوعدك حقًّا؟
If I drive them off, I'm done with chores. That's okay, right?
بمجرّد أن أبعدهم من هنا يمكنني التوقف عن العمل، صحيح؟
Couldn't ask for more.
.ما كنتُ لأرغب بغير هذا
This place can't take a year of your "chores."
إن عملتَ في المطعم لسنةٍ سيصير في حالةٍ لا يُحسد عليها
Alright!
!حسنًا
You seriously want to be King of the Pirates, kid?
أتريد أن تصبح ملك القراصنة فعلًا؟
As long as we take that ship, the Grand Line is nothing to be scared of!
!لا سبب يدعونا لخوف الغراند لاين إن استولينا على تلك السفينة
We can pull right up to an enemy ship for a more effective ambush!
...بإمكاننا شنّ هجوم مباغت على سفن الأعداء بأكثر فعاليّة
It's better than pretending to be a Marine ship or raising the white flag.
من أن نتظاهر أننا سفينة تابعة للبحرية أو أن نرفع علم الاستسلام...
It would be a perfect sneak attack.
.سنتمكّن من شنّ هجمات مباغتة مثاليَّة
It's true that no one would think...
...صحيحٌ أنَّ لا أحد سيشكّ
...pirates are on board such a goofy-looking ship.
أن قراصنةً قد يبحرون على متنِ سفينةٍ سخيفة كهذه
B-But Don... Even if we reenter the Grand Line with it,
،لـ-لكن أيها الدون... حتى إن دخلنا الغراند لاين بتلك السفينة
what if we come across someone like Hawk Eye Mihawk again?
...فإن صادفنا شخصًا مثل عين الصقر ميهوك ثانيةً
You're still afraid of someone like that? Huh?!
أما زلتم تهابون رجلًا مثله؟
N-No...
...كـ-كلا
You think an ordinary human can slice up a huge ship like that?!
أتعتقدون أنّ إنسانًا عاديًّا بوسعه تقطيع سفينة شراعية ضخمة؟
He must have a devil fruit power.
،لا بدّ أنها قدرة فاكهة شيطان
Although those with devil fruit powers are just myths to your average person,
،رغم أنّ آكلي فواكه الشيطان يراهم المجتمع كأساطير
the Grand Line is crawling with them.
.إلّا أنّ الغراند لاين يعجّ بهم
Mihawk must have used some strange power to carve up our ship.
ولا بدّ أنّ ميهوك استعمل قوّة غريبة ما لتقطيع سفينتنا
Even that Straw Hat brat will be just another pirate on that sea.
حتى فتى قبعة القش سيصير قرصانًا عاديًّا بمُجرَّد دخوله الغراند لاين
But Red Leg Zeff sailed there for an entire year.
،أمّا الساق الحمراء زيف فقد أبحر سنةً هُناك
He must have had ways of dealing with those monsters.
لا بُدَّ أن لديهم وسائلَ مُعيَّنة لمواجهة أولئك الوحوش
I'm certain those methods are recorded in his logbook!
ولا بدّ أنَّ تلك الوسائل مدوّنة في سجلّ سفينته
Perhaps he also wrote something about the One Piece.
وإن حالفنا الحظّ فقد نجد معلومات عن الون بيس حتى
Don Krieg's still got it!
!فهمت... هذا ما توقعته من الدون كريغ
With that ship and logbook, we can go after the One Piece again!
ما إن نملُك تلك السفينة وذاك السجل سنجد طريقنا للون بيس ثانيةً
Got that, guys?!
!أفهمتم يا رجال؟ لننطلق ونستولي على المطعم
– Yeah!
!أجل
This ship belongs to us, the cooks!
!هذه سفينتنا نحن، الطباخون
Go to the operating room and open up the fins.
اذهب إلى غرفة التشغيل وافتح الزعانف
What? Open up the fins?
ماذا؟ أفتحها؟
That'll give the enemy a foothold!
!سيمنح ذلك موطئ قدمٍ للعدو
I don't mind.
لا بأس، فالأفضل ألَّا يُصبح المطعم ساحة قتال
If a battle breaks out in there, the old fart will complain.
إن أصبح كذلك، فسيشتكي العجوز اللعين
Did you say something, you damn brat?
أقلتَ شيئًا أيها الشقيّ اللعين؟
Yeah, I said you like to complain! Now, go.
نعم، قلتُ أنّك ستتشكى. هيّا اذهب
O-Okay...!
...حـ-حاضر
They're coming, they're coming! They're finally coming!
!ها هم قادمون، قادمون أخيرًا
Here I go!
!ها أنا ذا
Gum-Gum Rocket!
غومو غومو نو
And...
...و
Gum-Gum...
غومو غومو نو
Check out the cabin boy! Not bad!
!إن العامل الجديد بارع
Wh-What the hell...
...مـ-من يكون
...is that guy?!
يا ترى؟
The Grand Line is crawling with guys like that?
أيعجّ الغراند لاين بأشخاصٍ مثله؟
Sanji!
!سانجي
Watch closely how he fights.
.راقب جيّدًا كيف يقاتل
I can't believe you attacked the same restaurant that fed you.
...لا أصدّق أنك تهاجم المطعم بعد أن قدّموا لك طعامًا
I'm gonna kick your ungrateful ass!
!سأوسعك ضربًا يا ناكر الجميل الوغد
You're going to fight on the water with hardly a foothold?
إذًا فأنت تريد القتال على الماء حيث لا موطئ قدم؟
At the very least, I know devil fruit users can't swim. Isn't that right,
لا حول لآكلي فاكهة الشّيطان .ولا قوّة في البحر. أنا أدرك ذلك
anchor boy?!
!ستكون أشبه بمرساة
Yep! I stretch instead!
.يمكنني التمدّد بدلًا من ذلك
Sanji! The fins are gonna open up now!
!سانجي! سأفتح الزّعانف الآن
A platform is rising...
...من تحت البحر
out of the sea!
!ظهر موطئ قدم
Now we can fight to our heart's content, you pirate scum!
!سنقاتل بكلّ ما لدينا أيها القراصنة الأوغاد
I see.
فهمت، وضعتم ساحة قتال حتى لا يتأذى المطعم بحدّ ذاته
That works out for us too, since that ship's gonna be ours.
،ذلك يناسبنا نحن أيضًا، فهذه السفينة صتصير لنا
This deal just keeps getting better.
.صرتُ أبتغي هذه السفينة أكثر
As if we'd let you have this restaurant!
!لن نسمح لك بأخذ هذا المطعم
That's right! Don't take us lightly!
!هذا صحيح، لا تستخفّ بنا
We're fighting cooks!
!نحن طباخون مقاتلون
Take to the seas, Mackerel Head I, the Baratie's very own battleship!
!أبحروا، سلاح معارك باراتي البحريّ، رأس الإسقمريّ 1
Unless you wanna sleep with the fishes, move!
!ليغادر حالًا من لا يريد الموت
What the hell is that?
ما هذا؟
So cool! I want one!
!هذا رائع، أنا أريده
Paddle faster!
!جدّف بسرعة أعلى
I'm trying!
!أنا أحاول
Fire!
!نار
I'm gonna fall in!
!أشعر بالغثيان
Alright! Good job!
!مرحى، أحسنتم عملًا
Patty! Carne! Give 'em hell!
!فلتنالا منهم يا باتي وكارني
They're pretty good!
!إنهما بارعان
Never mind those minnows! The big catch is up ahead!
!لا تشح نظرك، نحن نصوّب نحوه
Roger!
!أجل
Krieg! Get ready!
!استعد يا كريغ
Marvel at the power of the Sea Restaurant Baratie's oceangoing weapon!
!شاهدوا قوَّة سلاح معارك مطعم باراتي البحري
What? Did we bump into something?
ماذا؟ هل اصطدمنا بشيء؟
Huh? We're stuck!
!ماذا؟ لا يمكننا التحرك
I am Don Krieg...
!أنا الدون كريغ
the man who will rule this world's oceans!
!وأنا من سيُهيمن على محيطات العالم
I told you that's gonna be me!
أخبرتك أنّي من سيُهيمن عليها
I don't have time for your games!
!لا وقت لديّ لإضاعته مع ألعابكم
That's some killer strength!
!ما هذه القوّة الجبّارة؟
It's coming this way!
!إنّها قادمة ناحيتنا
It'll destroy the restaurant!
!سيُدمّر المطعم
– Sanji!
!سانجي
With... just his foot?!
!بساقه؟
S-Such strong legs!
!يـ-يا لقوَّة ساقه
He kicked that weird boat away!
!لقد ركل ذلك القارب الغريب
That foot technique...
...تقنية الساق هذه
He's pretty good!
!إنّه بارع
Sanji, you son of a bitch!
!أيها الوغد سانجي
You tryin' to crush your allies?!
أتحاول تحطيم حلفائك؟
Yeah.
...نعم
Don't "yeah" us, you crazy stew!
!لا تُجب بـ«نعم» أيها الحساء المجنون
You just about lost your strongest allies, spaghetti head!
!كدتَ تفقد مساعدين أقوياء أيها المعكرونة الأبله
Is this really the best time for you cooks to be cracking jokes?
أتظنون أن لديكم وقت للمزاح أيها الطباخون؟
Let's get them!
!لننل منهم
Even with a weapon, a cook's just a cook.
.يبقى الطباخ طباخًا وإن حمل سلاحًا
We seasoned fighters are way out of your league.
خبرتنا في القتال في مستوى مختلف عنكم تمامًا
Now, behave yourselves and go find a restaurant on solid ground.
فأحسنوا التصرف وافتحوا لكم مطعمًا على البرّ أيها الطباخون
Hey, you guys! Why are you letting them mop the floor with you?!
!أنتم
Aren't you fighting cooks?!
!أما زلتم تدعون أنفسكم طباخين مقاتلين؟
They're not like anyone we've fought before!
إن مستواهم مختلفٍ كليًّا عمّن نقاتلهم دومًا
Don't go thinking we're anything like your average pirates.
لا تضعونا في كفّة القراصنة العاديين
We're the Krieg Pirates, conquerors of the East Blue.
فنحن قراصنة المُهيمن على الأزرق الشرقي، الدون كريغ
By decree of the Krieg Pirates, this ship is already ours!
!بأمرٍ من قراصنة كريغ، أمست هذه السفينة ملكًا لنا سلفًا
I've been a cook for over a decade.
.أنا طباخ لأزيد من عشر سنوات
I've worked for 300 restaurants.
.زرتُ 300 مطعمًا
I always got fired for starting fights, and life was rough.
لطالما طُردت لتسببي بالشجارات، وقد عشتُ حياةً قاسية
After countless restaurants, we finally came here...
...لجأنا لهذا المطعم أخيرًا بعد ذهابنا من مطعم لآخر
Anybody there?!
!فيه أحد؟
Help Wanted
مطلوب مساعدة
Is this the restaurant run by Red Leg Zeff?!
أهذا المطعم المُدار من قِبل زيف الساق الحمراء؟
This "Damn Cooks Wanted" poster better be true!
أرجو أن يكون موضوع استقبالكم للطباخين اللُّعناء صحيحًا
Yeah, it's true.
.نعم، إنه صحيح
Be they master criminals or escaped convicts,
،سواء أكانوا مجرمين خطيرين أو هاربين من السجن
if they're starving and find their way to this restaurant,
،إن أرادوا الأكل بشدّة وعثروا على هذا المطعم
we'll feed them until they're stuffed.
!فسنطعمهم إلى أن يشبعوا
Can you handle that?!
!أبإمكانكما تحمّل ذلك؟
– Y-Yes, Chef!
!حـ-حاضر
Help Wanted
مطلوب مساعدة
We can't serve this vile soup to paying customers!
!لا يمكننا تقديم حساء قذر كهذا للزبائن
What did you hit me for?!
!لمَ ضربتني؟
It's a mark of resolve!
!تلك علامة العزيمة
Shut up!
!اخرس
Be it brawling or cooking, we're allowed to do whatever we like.
...الشجار والطبخ... مسموحٌ لنا فعل ما يحلو لنا
No other restaurant compares!
.لا مطعم آخر أفضل من هذا
So they say.
.سمعتهما
Got that, Krieg?
أتدرك الآن يا كريغ؟
In the kitchen, every day is a fierce battle.
تكريس أنفسنا للطبخ يوميًا يُعدُّ معركة حامية
Compared to that, the pirates we're facing today are nothing!
مقارنة بذلك، فالقراصنة الذين نواجههم اليوم لا شيء
He's exactly right!
!معك حق
Fight!
!فلنقاتل
– Yeah!
!أجل
Protect Chef Zeff!
!احموا المالك
Protect the restaurant!
!احموا المطعم
Wh-Who the...?
...هـ-هذا
What are you guys doing?
ماذا تفعلون يا جماعة؟
What's up with that weirdo?
من هذا؟
Pearl "the Invincible" Commander, Second Unit Krieg Pirates
بيرل المنيع قائد الوحدة الثانية لقراصنة كريغ
Unassailable: hence invincible!
!أنا جدار حصين، وهذا يعني أنّي منيع
The invincible member of the Krieg Pirates,
أنا رجل الدّرع المنيع في قراصنة كريغ
Pearl, at your service.
!وبيرل-سان هو اسمي
Pearl!
!بيرل-سان
Patty! Carne! Are you all right?!
هل أنتما بخير يا باتي وكارني؟
They're not all right because they received a Pearl Present, my killer punch.
ليسا بخير، فقد تلقيا لكمتي القاتلة، هدية بيرل
Oh, he's got a nice knife! Well, it's mine now.
!يا لجودة هذه السكين، سآخذها
Hey, let go. Give it to me! Let it go, you damn loser!
!اتركها، أعطني إياها، أفلتها أيها الفاشل
He sure can kick!
!لديه ركلات جيّدة حقًّا
A kitchen knife is a cook's soul.
.سكين المطبخ هي روح الطباخ
Keep your dirty hands off it, amateurs.
!لا تلمسوها بتهوّر أيها الهواة
Sanji...
...سانجي
Hold tight to this and stay down.
.أمسك هذه جيّدًا وابقَ مستلقيًا
I'll clean up this trash.
.سأهتمّ بأمرهم
We won't be beaten by a mere cook!
!لن نسمح لطباخ وضيع بهزيمتنا
"A mere cook"?
أقلتم طباخ وضيع؟
Then how about I fillet you bastards?!
ما رأيكم أن أقطعكم يا أوغاد؟
You're pretty arrogant to cast them aside with just kicks.
يا لوقاحتك لهزيمتهم بركلاتك فحسب
Is that some sort of policy?
أهذه سياستك؟
A cook's hands are his livelihood.
.اليدان عنصر مهمّ لأيّ طباخ
I can't risk them in a fight.
لا يمكنني إيذاؤهما في المعارك
These legs will take you down as well.
.سأطيح بك بساقي هذه أيضًا
Take me down?
تطيح بي؟
Ridiculous.
.هذا مُحالٌ
I'm an invincible man who's won all sixty-one of my battles without a scratch.
أنا رجل منيع فزتُ كلّ معاركي الواحدة والستين بلا خدوش
I've never shed blood in battle,
،ما نزفتُ في معركة قط
not even a single drop.
ولو قطرة واحدة
Winning unharmed is proof of my power.
،الفوز بلا خدوشٍ برهانٌ واضحٌ على قوَّتي
I'm a shield man and a gentleman.
.أنا رجل درع كلّي أناقة
Elegant, am I not?
أوَليست هذه لباقة؟
Did he make a joke? It wasn't funny at all.
أهذه مزحة؟ لم تكن مضحكة أبدًا
Hey, Straw Hat brat!
!يا فتى قبعة القش
Pay attention or you'll get hurt!
!ستتأذى إلّم تنتبه
Even battleship cannons can't hurt me.
حتى مدافع السّفن الحربيّة لا تنفع ضدّي
I come out of any attack unharmed!
!أخرج سالمًا معافى من أيّ هجوم
Good thing I didn't fall in the sea.
جيدٌ أني لم أسقط في البحر
What?
ماذا؟
Well, shit.
.هذا سيّئ
Blood! Oh, no!
!دماء، مصيبة
Pearl, don't worry!
.لا تقلق يا بيرل-سان
It's just a nosebleed!
!إنّه مجرد نزيف أنف
It's not as if you were wounded in battle!
!كما أنه ليس جرحًا من معركة
Please calm down, Pearl!
!هدّئ من روعك يا بيرل-سان
What's going on?
ماذا يحدث؟
Th-Th-Th-Th-These guys are dangerous!
!هـ-هـ-هؤلاء خطيرون
What's his deal? He's acting weird.
.ما باله؟ بدأ يتصرف بغرابة
Is a nosebleed that big a deal?
ما قصّة نزيف أنفه؟
Stop it, Pearl!
!توقف يا بيرل
It's just a nosebleed! Don't lose your cool!
!لا تفقد أعصابك لمجرد نزيف أنف
What the heck is he about to do?
ما الذي ينوي فعله؟
Danger! Danger! Danger!
!خطر، خطر، خطر
Oh, no! It's started!
!مصيبة، لقد بدأ
When Pearl loses his cool, he actually ignites!
!يشتعل بيرل-سان حين يغضب
What was that?
ما كان هذا؟
Fire Pearl...
تايو بيرل
Blowout!
داي توكتين
Pearl! Please stop!
!أرجوك توقف يا بيرل-سان
Burn! Between this blaze and my flaming shield,
،احترقوا! بلهيبي هذا ودرعي الملتهب
you have no idea how invincible I am!
!لا فكرة لديكم عن مدى مناعتي
Moron! He'll burn down the ship we're commandeering!
أسيحرق ذلك الغبي السفينةَ التي نُريد الاستيلاء عليها؟
Ow, ow, ow, ow...
...مؤلم مؤلم مؤلم مؤلم
Dammit!
!سُحقًا
This isn't good! The restaurant will catch fire!
!هذا سيئ، سيحترق المطعم
The restaurant will burn?
سيحترق المطعم؟
Burn! Burn!
!احترق، احترق
You son of a bitch!
!أيها الوغد
You'll get flambéed, Sanji!
!يا أحمق، ستحترق يا سانجي
I'm not gonna let you...
...لن أسمح لك بإحراق هذا المطعم ببساطة
Wh-What a lunatic!
!يـ-يا لشدّة تهوره
Does he want to be a human torch?!
!أيريد التحول لشعلة بشريّة؟
Even feral beasts steer clear of Fire Pearl!
...حتى الحيوانات الضارية لا تقترب من لآلئي النارية
Dumbass!
!أيها الغبي
No cook worth their salt is afraid of a little fire!
لا أجدر بكوني طباخًا إن خفت من مجرّد ألسنة لهب
D-Dammit!
!سـ-سحقًا، يـ-يا للباقة هذا الرجل
Here I come!
!ها أنا ذا
That was a solid hit!
!أصابته مباشرة
He broke through Pearl the Invincible's wall!
!تمكّن من إسقاط بيرل-سان رغم درعه المنيع
What's with this cook?
ما بال هذا الطباخ؟ إنه خطير حقًّا
Y-Y-You insufferable...
!أ-أ-أيها الوغد
I need to fuel more fire pearls!
!عليّ إطعام لآلئي النارية أكثر
No, the restaurant...!
!سيحترق المطعم
If the fire reaches the kitchen, it'll explode!
!إن وصلت النيران للمطبخ، فسينفجر المطعم
Chef Zeff! Please get out of the way!
!أيها المالك! اهرب رجاءً أيها المالك
M-My fire pearls!
...لآ-لآلئي النارية
That was child's play!
!هذا أشبه بلعب أطفال
The gust from his kick put out the flame!
!أطفأت رياح ركلته النار
Oh, wow! That guy's superhuman!
!يا لضراوته، لا بُدَّ أنَّها تقنية إلهية
So Red Leg Zeff is still kicking?!
أما زال زيف الساق الحمراء قويًّا كسابق عهده؟
That was awesome, Boss Man!
!العم مذهل، أثار إعجابي حقًّا
Now that it's come to this,
،بما أنّ الأمر آل لهذا الحال
I'll sink you all with the fins before the restaurant catches fire!
فسأغرقكم مع تلك الزعانف قبل أن يشتعل المطعم
Sanji! Watch out!
!انتبه يا سانجي
Oh no! He's surrounded by the blaze!
!لا جدوى فالنيرانُ تحاصره
Ow, ow, ow...
...هذا ساخن
Cabin Boy!
!الفتى العامل
Gum-Gum Bazooka!
غومو غومو نو
He knocked that iron ball back! Ow, ow, ow...
!ردَّ الكرة الحديدية إلى حيث أتت
Pearl is really down this time!
!هُزم بيرل-سان كليًّا الآن
– Pearl...!
...بيرل-سان قد
What the hell?
ماذا؟
That guy sure was a dummy.
.يا لغبائه
They're all worthless...
...لا يُرجى من أحد
In the end, I can only rely on myself.
.لا أحد يُعتمد عليه غيري
The battle ends here.
.ستنتهي هذه المعركة هنا